No, it's a gentle kick;
you're doing it wrong.
(Raj:)Here. Give me those.
(Howard:)Uh, maybe it was
more of a circle?
(Bernadette:)It's weird that guy thought
you were a couple.
Yes!
(Howard:)See?
(Howard:)Easy. And look at
all this cargo space.
(Amy:)You know,
we'll get the crib out
(Howard:)and you can take it
for a test-drive.
(Howard:)I'm telling you,
this van is gonna be...
(Bernadette:)Oh, is it your back?
Uh... yeah.
(Howard:)Anyway, let's just get
in and see if the GPS
(Howard:)can take us to the
nearest emergency room.
(Sheldon:)So until
Amy's apartment is fixed,
(Sheldon:)she and I
are living here together.
(Bert:)I lived with my old girlfriend.
(Bert:)She was a geologist, too.
(Amy:)Things didn't work out?
(Bert:)I came home from work one day
and she had taken everything.